Hello everyone welcome to Digital Investment
Gyan, today we will talk about how to change
your nominee in ICICI Pashal Life Insurance,
basically there is no online option in online life insurance,
so you are requested to
watch the video till the end, so
whether you want to keep this ICC in multiple lots
or single lots, all those
doubts will be cleared, so do
watch the video till the end.  Let's get started.
Now see, in this we have entered life
insurance, as soon as we enter the ICI of ICCI, we will
click on ICI Life Insurance India.  As soon as you click, you will see that this
option of login is showing in a corner,
you will click on the individual login.
Click on Login Individual written on the right side.
After clicking, see here the option of your
mobile number has come.
Password: Suppose you have not kept a password, then if you
click on the option below, Login by OTP, then an
OTP will come on your registered mobile number, as
we are entering this number,
see, we have clicked on Login, we will
enter the Login OTP mobile number here, as soon as you
enter the mobile number,
you will have to enter your date of birth, you will
enter your date of birth, only then
it will be verified.  This will enter.
Click on submit date of birth.
They are asking you to send OTP to both your email and mobile.
Sent it.
Now you will receive OTP.
Same OTP will come in both.  Enter any one OTP and
submit it.
Your submission has been done.  Whatever ICCI
PDL plan you have, now the
policy number and everything is visible here.  You will
click on the policy from which you want to make changes.
Clicking will scroll down.   They will
come down after choosing the policy.  This
policy is Snapchat.  Whatever details you have, you will be able to
see them.
After doing that, come down.  After coming down,
see, this option will be for profile
update.  Update Nomen Details by clicking on Update Profile.
After clicking on this,
choose your college number.  Whoever your
nominee is already, you can see this.
Then we will click on Change Name.
After adding, you will enter the nominee who is your first name and
his/her nominee.  I am
telling you exactly step by step.
You must watch the video till the end.  So,
you will not have any doubt in any section
or will not skip it.  After we enter this, we will
enter this relation.  Then
enter the date of birth of the nominee.
Then you will enter your gender.  Then
they will enter what your relationship is with them.
If you are keeping multiple nominees then
you have to make the percentage there 50%.
Whatever, let's say we have to keep four people and make it
25%.  If you want to keep only one then
you will submit it after completing it 100%.  Like
I'm keeping multiple two.  So that's
why I gave you that 50% above.  Now
we will add a nominee below and that too 50%.
Enter first name and last name.
They will enter their date of birth.
They will enter their gender.
When we come down to the submit page and
click on all, then see this, your
confirmation code will come on your email ID and
mobile number, the confirmation code in both
is the same code, you will enter it and click on submit.
If you are new to this channel then do
not forget to subscribe to the channel.  If this
video has helped you in any way, then
share the link of the video and like it.
If anything helps, do
n't
forget to subscribe to the channel.  This session took some time so
it expired.  If you click OK then it will be done
automatically.  The activation code will come
to your mobile.  You must have given the list number in it.  It will be
showing on the side.
I am telling you this online by entering that number.
Suppose you do not have a mobile number or email
ID, then you will have to go offline.
What cannot be done online.  You will
enter this.  Enter the OTP received on your mobile and
then click on submit.   It is taking
some time for the OTP to arrive.
OTP has arrived.
Now we will press enter and submit.
Look at this, your request has been
successfully submitted and will be
proceeded with within six days.
This will update your